Devesh Mhatre

Senior Frontend Developer

9028250240 deveshmhtr.mhatre92@gmail.com devesh-mhatre.netlify.app Pen, India

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

04/2021 - 01/2024

- Develop and maintain front-end properties across multiple frameworks, including ReactJS, NextJS, AngularJS, Rails (ERB)
- Develop, distribute and maintain React Native apps on Google Play Store and Apple App Store
- Lead React Native upgrade activities for compatibility with new Android and iOS versions
- Collaborate with managers, designers and QA engineers for requirement gathering before beginning development
- Collaborate with backend developers to integrate RESTful APIs with both web-based and app-based front-ends

Digital Marketing Intern

01/2021 - 04/2021

- · Manage social media accounts using Hootsuite
- · Manage company blog using WordPress
- · Design and write content for social media marketing

Business Development Intern

Cuemath *¬*

10/2018 - 01/2019

- Corresponded with prospective customers and partners
- · Conducted live seminars and product demos
- · Helped automate daily report generation process

EDUCATION

Business Administration (Marketing)
Tilak Maharashtra Vidapeeth, Pune

06/2016 - 05/2019

Bachelor's

SUMMARY

I am a senior front-end developer with three years of meaningful contributions, both as a sole product owner and as part of teams of varying size and scope. I have experience driving projects forward as the front-end development team lead, regardless of whether it's a legacy project or a new concept. I aim to tackle more complex problems and continue to find ways of improving user experience.

SKILLS

ReactJS

React Native

NextJS

NodeJS

AngularJS

Rails

Javascript

Typescript

Ruby

Git

Redux

LANGUAGES

English Native

Marathi Native

Hindi Native